<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Leo&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>https://LeoTheBestCoder.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Leo&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 00:56:38 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://LeoTheBestCoder.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Self Introduction</title>
      <link>https://LeoTheBestCoder.github.io/posts/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 15:35:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://LeoTheBestCoder.github.io/posts/intro/</guid>
      <description>I come from Taichung, a heartwarming city in central Taiwan.
I spent my high school years in class of math and science gifted students at Taichung Municipal Taichung Second Senior High School, during which I made many good friends and obtained countless amazing memories.
At July 2018, I finished my ultimate mission in high school — Advanced Subjects Test — and was luckily admitted to Department of Electrical Engineering at National Tsing Hua University (NTHU EE).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MeiChu Hackathon 梅竹黑客松</title>
      <link>https://LeoTheBestCoder.github.io/posts/meichu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 15:25:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://LeoTheBestCoder.github.io/posts/meichu/</guid>
      <description>Date 2020/10/24 (Sat.) - 2020/10/25 (Sun.)
Topic Logitech International: Ethical gaming world
Description There are increasingly more online games in recent years. When playing, we don&amp;rsquo;t want to encounter cheating behaviors that will decrease our will to play. Thus, we want to develop a cheating detection system that can detect unethical actions in online games.
Members  Handsome Leo (Me) Bo Wei Chen Jack Liu Bowen Lee Howard Wang  Ways of &amp;ldquo;Cheating&amp;rdquo;  gaming hack AFK (away from keyboard) ask other people to play etc  Solution: Machine Learning We surveyed a paper[1] focusing on remote suspicious mouse intrusion, which gave us some inspiraiton.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Undergraduate Research</title>
      <link>https://LeoTheBestCoder.github.io/posts/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 22:07:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://LeoTheBestCoder.github.io/posts/research/</guid>
      <description>Topic A Study on Active Learning for Improving Object Detection Model in Home Care System Using Limited Amount of Data
Members  Teammate: Jack Liu Mentor: Kuan Hung Chen  About Our Lab I am a member of NTHU Vision Science Lab (VSLAB) instructed by Prof. Min Sun.
Motivation In recent years, the population of the elderly keeps increasing. Therefore, our lab founded CarePLUS Group with the aim to develop a home care system, monitoring the action of the elderly and detect whether they are in danger using computer vision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ML成績爭議完整對話內容</title>
      <link>https://LeoTheBestCoder.github.io/posts/ml/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 00:56:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://LeoTheBestCoder.github.io/posts/ml/</guid>
      <description>06/30 20:48 (Me)
 助教您好： 我是ML學生107061218謝霖泳，我對我的總成績感到非常奇怪，以下是我的所有成績，請問等第A是如何計算出來的？ 學生 謝霖泳 敬上
   06/30 22:04 (TA)
 同學你好: 你們的final presentation分數是78，排名分數是88，最後還有做分數的微調，同學的分數剛好落在89。
TA
   06/30 22:25 (Me)
 助教您好： 有幾個地方想請教您。
  1.想請問final presentation的分數是被扣在什麼地方，因為我覺得我們整個呈現都算完整，也得到很不錯的結果(總成績整個平台第三名)，但卻得到如此不理想的分數78分，我們感到非常難過，請問老師、助教分別都打幾分？我們被扣了整整22分是分別被扣在那些地方呢？最後的78分又是如何計算出來的呢？
  2.想請問排名的88分是如何計算的，我們最後的成績在整個平台的前三名，但竟然一口氣被扣了12分，想請問排名分數的計算依據。
  3.想請問final presentation及排名的分數既然可能被打的這麼低，為何不公開透明地公布在eeclass的平台讓大家知道？且送成績前也沒有收到成績確認信，這樣是否會造成學生無法知道自己的總成績是如何計算出來的？
  4.最後想請問所謂「分數的微調」明確指的是什麼？如何「微調」學生的成績？
  再麻煩助教回覆，謝謝助教，辛苦了。
  學生 謝霖泳 敬上
   06/30 23:32 (TA)
 同學你好:
  1.presentation的分數是我們三位助教聽完各別主題各組的報告後，給予排名，平均後，換算成對應的分數，你們在該主題的平均排名是第7，換算成分數是78。
  2.你們在該主題的排名是第3，換算成對應的分數是88。
* 排名與分數的對應表經助教們討論後依序如下: 93、91、88、86、83、81、78、76、73、71、68</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IC Lab</title>
      <link>https://LeoTheBestCoder.github.io/posts/iclab/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 14:27:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://LeoTheBestCoder.github.io/posts/iclab/</guid>
      <description>Interesting course! Cool!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intern at ITRI</title>
      <link>https://LeoTheBestCoder.github.io/posts/intern/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 14:26:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://LeoTheBestCoder.github.io/posts/intern/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
