<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Leo&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>https://LeoTheBestCoder.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Leo&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 14:27:53 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://LeoTheBestCoder.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Self Introduction</title>
      <link>https://LeoTheBestCoder.github.io/posts/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 15:35:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://LeoTheBestCoder.github.io/posts/intro/</guid>
      <description>I come from Taichung, a heartwarming city in central Taiwan.
I spent my high school years in class of math and science gifted students at Taichung Municipal Taichung Second Senior High School, during which I made many good friends and obtained countless amazing memories.
At July 2018, I finished my ultimate mission in high school — Advanced Subjects Test — and was luckily admitted to Department of Electrical Engineering at National Tsing Hua University (NTHU EE).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MeiChu Hackathon 梅竹黑客松</title>
      <link>https://LeoTheBestCoder.github.io/posts/meichu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 15:25:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://LeoTheBestCoder.github.io/posts/meichu/</guid>
      <description>Date 2020/10/24 (Sat.) - 2020/10/25 (Sun.)
Topic Logitech International: Ethical gaming world
Description There are increasingly more online games in recent years. When playing, we don&amp;rsquo;t want to encounter cheating behaviors that will decrease our will to play. Thus, we want to develop a cheating detection system that can detect unethical actions in online games.
Members  Handsome Leo (Me) Bo Wei Chen Jack Liu Bowen Lee Howard Wang  Ways of &amp;ldquo;Cheating&amp;rdquo;  gaming hack AFK (away from keyboard) ask other people to play etc  Solution: Machine Learning We surveyed a paper[1] focusing on remote suspicious mouse intrusion, which gave us some inspiraiton.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Undergraduate Research</title>
      <link>https://LeoTheBestCoder.github.io/posts/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 22:07:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://LeoTheBestCoder.github.io/posts/research/</guid>
      <description>Topic A Study on Active Learning for Improving Object Detection Model in Home Care System Using Limited Amount of Data
Members  Teammate: Jack Liu Mentor: Kuan Hung Chen  About Our Lab I am a member of NTHU Vision Science Lab (VSLAB) instructed by Prof. Min Sun.
Motivation In recent years, the population of the elderly keeps increasing. Therefore, our lab founded CarePLUS Group with the aim to develop a home care system, monitoring the action of the elderly and detect whether they are in danger using computer vision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ICLAB</title>
      <link>https://LeoTheBestCoder.github.io/posts/iclab/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 14:27:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://LeoTheBestCoder.github.io/posts/iclab/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intern at ITRI</title>
      <link>https://LeoTheBestCoder.github.io/posts/intern/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 14:26:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://LeoTheBestCoder.github.io/posts/intern/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
